Outer Banks History Center Ephemera Collection PC.5276
State Archives of North Carolina
- North Carolina Counties, 1798-2019 and undated; 43990; Outer Banks History Center
  - Dare, 1881-2019 and undated; 4659; Outer Banks History Center
    - Real Estate, 1927-2016 and undated; 4668; Outer Banks History Center
      - Resort Rodanthe, undated; 4911; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Resort Rodanthe)
      - Roanoke Island Real Estate, circa 1960s-2000s; 4912; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Roanoke Island Real Estate)
      - Rollason Realty (Kill Devil Hills), 1983-1984 and undated; 4913; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Rollason Realty (Kill Devil Hills))
      - Sanderling (Duck), 1992-2007 and undated; 4914; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Sanderling (Duck))
      - Seagate Realty (Kill Devil Hills), 1984-1988; 4915; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Seagate Realty (Kill Devil Hills))
      - Sea Scape (Kitty Hawk), 1982 and undated; 4916; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Sea Scape (Kitty Hawk))
      - Seaside Realty (Kitty Hawk), 1993-1996; 4917; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Seaside Realty (Kitty Hawk))
      - Sea Oats Realty (Kill Devil Hills), 1993-1994; 4918; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Sea Oats Realty (Kill Devil Hills))
      - Southern Shores Real Estate, 1966-1980 and undated; 4919; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Southern Shores Real Estate)
      - Southern Shores Realty, circa 1950s-1995; 4920; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Southern Shores Realty)
      - Southern Shores Realty [2 folders], circa 1950s-1995; 4921; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Southern Shores Realty [2 folders])
      - Sun Realty, 1983-1997; 4922; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Sun Realty)
      - Surf or Sound (Avon), 1984-1996; 4923; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Surf or Sound (Avon))
      - Todd Realty (Kill Devil Hills), 1983-1985; 4924; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Todd Realty (Kill Devil Hills))
      - Twiddy & Company Realtors (Duck), 1985-1995; 4925; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Twiddy & Company Realtors (Duck))
      - The Village Link, 1996-1999; 4926; Outer Banks History Center (Folder The Village Link)
      - Village Realty (Nags Head), 1990-2016; 4927; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Village Realty (Nags Head))
      - Vintage Vacations (Kitty Hawk), 1995-1996; 4928; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Vintage Vacations (Kitty Hawk))
      - Virginia Dare Shores Promotional Booklet, 1927; 4929; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Virginia Dare Shores Promotional Booklet)
      - Wright Realty, 1982-1985; 4930; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Wright Realty)
      - Young People (Kill Devil Hills), 1969-1992; 4931; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Young People (Kill Devil Hills))
    - Churches and Religious Services, 1946-2016 and undated; 4669; Outer Banks History Center
      Materials in this series primarily consist of historical sketches, flyers, and programs for events and services conducted at three Dare County churches: Manteo Baptist Church, Mt. Olivet United Methodist Church, and St. Andrew's By-the-Sea Episcopal Church.
      - Manteo Baptist Church [2 folders], 1970-1998; 4932; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Manteo Baptist Church [2 folders])
      - Mt. Olivet United Methodist Church, 1946-circa 1990; 4933; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Mt. Olivet United Methodist Church)
      - St. Andrews By-the-Sea Episcopal Church, 1993-2016 and undated; 4934; Outer Banks History Center (Folder St. Andrews By-the-Sea Episcopal Church)
    - Political Ephemera, 1956-2017; 4670; Outer Banks History Center
      This series contains material related to local elections held in Dare County, including sample ballots for Dare County residents and campaign materials created by various candidates. Materials in this subseries only relate to local elections; documentation of state and national campaigns can be found in the State of North Carolina series.
      - Campaign Materials, 1962-1996; 4935; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Campaign Materials)
      - Campaign Materials, 1998-2017; 4936; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Campaign Materials)
      - Sample Ballots, 1956-2001; 4937; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Sample Ballots)
  - Davidson, 1959-1994; 4938; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Davidson)
  - Davie, 1968; 4939; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Davie)
  - Duplin, 1949, circa 1980s-1990s; 4940; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Duplin)
  - Durham, 1900-1997 and undated; 4941; Outer Banks History Center
    - Businesses, circa 1960s-1977; 23014; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Businesses)
    - Duke University [2 folders], 1900-1993 and undated; 23015; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Duke University [2 folders])
    - Historic Stagville, 1978-1996; 23016; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Historic Stagville)
    - Organizations, 1992-1997 and undated; 23017; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Organizations)
  - Edgecombe, 1956-circa 1990s; 4942; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Edgecombe)
  - Forsyth, 1976-2005; 4943; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Forsyth)
  - Gaston, undated; 4944; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Gaston)
  - Gates, 1976-1988; 4945; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Gates)
  - Granville, 1914, 2007; 4946; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Granville)
  - Guilford [2 folders], 1888-1996 and undated; 4947; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Guilford [2 folders])
  - Halifax, undated; 4948; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Halifax)
  - Harnett, circa 1960s-1995; 4949; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Harnett)
  - Haywood, circa 1960s-1970s; 4950; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Haywood)
  - Henderson, 1964 and undated; 4951; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Henderson)
  - Hertford, 1985 and undated; 4952; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Hertford)
  - Hertford: Chowan College, circa 1990s; 4953; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Hertford: Chowan College)
  - Hyde, 1939-2016 and undated; 4954; Outer Banks History Center
    - Hyde (General), 1939-2016; 4955; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Hyde (General))
    - Businesses, 1967-2013 and undated; 4956; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Businesses)
    - Organizations [2 folders], 1949-2016; 4957; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Organizations [2 folders])
  - Iredell, undated; 5263; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Iredell)
  - Jackson, undated; 5264; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Jackson)
  - Johnston, 1995 and undated; 5265; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Johnston)
  - Lenoir, 1964-2006 and undated; 5266; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Lenoir)
  - Macon, 1992; 5267; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Macon)
  - Madison, 1886; 5268; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Madison)
  - Martin, undated; 5269; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Martin)
  - McDowell, undated; 5270; Outer Banks History Center (Folder McDowell)
  - Mecklenburg, 1934-1987 and undated; 5271; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Mecklenburg)
  - Mecklenburg: Davidson College, 1888-1985; 5272; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Mecklenburg: Davidson College)
  - Mitchell, undated; 5273; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Mitchell)
  - Moore, 1992-1996; 5274; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Moore)
  - Nash, 1914-2005; 5275; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Nash)
  - New Hanover, 1858-2006 and undated; 4971; Outer Banks History Center
    - Businesses, 1932-1997 and undated; 23018; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Businesses)
    - Cape Fear Museum, 1995; 23019; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Cape Fear Museum)
    - Fort Fisher Aquarium, 1977-1998; 23020; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Fort Fisher Aquarium)
    - Lower Cape Fear Historical Society, 1956-2006; 23021; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Lower Cape Fear Historical Society)
    - Organizations [2 folders], 1858-1997 and undated; 23022; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Organizations [2 folders])
    - Pamlico-Tar River Foundation, 1990-1995; 23023; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Pamlico-Tar River Foundation)
    - Promotional Brochures: Carolina Beach, Cape Fear Coast, Kure Beach, Wilmington, Wrightsville Beach, circa 1950s-1990s; 29674; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Promotional Brochures: Carolina Beach, Cape Fear Coast, Kure Beach, Wilmington, Wrightsville Beach)
    - Recreation, 1996 and undated; 23024; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Recreation)
    - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices, 1957-1974; 23025; Outer Banks History Center (Folder U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices)
    - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices, 1975-1986; 23026; Outer Banks History Center (Folder U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices)
    - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices, 1975-1986; 23027; Outer Banks History Center (Folder U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices)
    - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices, 1975-1977; 23028; Outer Banks History Center (Folder U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices)
    - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices, 1978-1979; 23029; Outer Banks History Center (Folder U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices)
    - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices, 1980; 23030; Outer Banks History Center (Folder U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices)
    - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices, 1981-1982; 23031; Outer Banks History Center (Folder U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices)
    - U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices [4 folders], 1991-1994; 23032; Outer Banks History Center (Folder U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Wilmington District Public Notices [4 folders])
    - U.S.S. North Carolina, circa 1960-1994; 23033; Outer Banks History Center (Folder U.S.S. North Carolina)
  - Northampton, 1921-1991; 5277; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Northampton)
  - Onslow, 1992-1996 and undated; 5278; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Onslow)
  - Orange, 1951-1998 and undated; 5279; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Orange)
  - Orange: Businesses, 1992 and undated; 5280; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Orange: Businesses)
  - Pamlico, 1988-1995 and undated; 5281; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Pamlico)
  - Pasquotank, 1928-2010 and undated; 4977; Outer Banks History Center
    - Pasquotank (general) [2 folders], circa 1940-2006 and undated; 23034; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Pasquotank (general) [2 folders])
    - College of the Albemarle, 1961-2007; 23035; Outer Banks History Center (Folder College of the Albemarle)
    - Museum of the Albemarle, 1976-2010; 23036; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Museum of the Albemarle)
    - Real Estate Showcase, 1995-1996; 23037; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Real Estate Showcase)
    - Recreation [2 folders], 1952-1972; 23038; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Recreation [2 folders])
    - U.S. Coast Guard Air Station, 1940-1992; 23039; Outer Banks History Center (Folder U.S. Coast Guard Air Station)
  - Pender, 1975 and undated; 5283; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Pender)
  - Perquimans, 1943-2004 and undated; 4979; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Perquimans)
  - Pitt, 1905-2004; 4980; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Pitt)
  - Polk, undated; 4981; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Polk)
  - Randolph, 1995 and undated; 4982; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Randolph)
  - Richmond, undated; 4983; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Richmond)
  - Robeson, 1993 and undated; 4984; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Robeson)
  - Rowan, 1996 and undated; 4985; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Rowan)
  - Sampson, 1966; 4986; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Sampson)
  - Scotland, undated; 4987; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Scotland)
  - Stanley, 1928 and undated; 4988; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Stanley)
  - Swain, 1975-1992; 4989; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Swain)
  - Tyrrell, 1979-2005; 4990; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Tyrrell)
  - Union, 1968, 1973; 4991; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Union)
  - Wake, 1917-1999 and undated; 4992; Outer Banks History Center
    - Wake (general), 1946-1993 and undated; 23040; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Wake (general))
    - Businesses, 1993-1995 and undated; 23041; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Businesses)
    - Organizations [2 folders], 1917-1999; 23042; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Organizations [2 folders])
    - Raleigh Chamber of Commerce, 1930-1962 and undated; 23043; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Raleigh Chamber of Commerce)
  - Warren, undated; 4993; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Warren)
  - Washington, 1977-2018 and undated; 4994; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Washington)
  - Watauga, circa 1960s-1990s; 4995; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Watauga)
  - Wayne, 1970 and undated; 4996; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Wayne)
  - Wilkes, undated; 4997; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Wilkes)
  - Wilson, 1948-circa 1990s; 4998; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Wilson)
  - Yancey, 1926-circa 1960s; 4999; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Yancey)
- State of North Carolina, 1825-2016 and undated; 43991; Outer Banks History Center
  This subseries contains materials related to the state of North Carolina generally, as well as regions within the state. Materials include brochures, event programs, published editions of speeches and memorial tributes, political circulars and campaign materials, tourists' guides, and other printed material. Materials are arranged into five subseries: State Agencies and Organizations, 1850-2015 and undated; Events, 1866-2003; Recreation, 1915-2001; and Political Ephemera, 1825-2016 and undated.
  - State Agencies and Organizations, 1850-2015 and undated; 4671; Outer Banks History Center
    The State Agencies and Organizations subseries, 1850-2015 and undated, contains materials created by or related to various clubs, professional and trade groups, organizations, agencies, and offices active in the state of North Carolina. Included in this subseries are documents related to individual divisions, departments, and offices within the North Carolina state government, including the North Carolina General Assembly and Office of the Governor. Materials primarily include pamphlets, brochures, event flyers, reports, form letters, and promotional material.
    - Agricultural Extension Service, 1959-1990; 5305; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Agricultural Extension Service)
    - Agricultural Groups, 1856-1997; 5306; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Agricultural Groups)
    - Albemarle-Pamlico Estuarine Study, 1988-1993; 5307; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Albemarle-Pamlico Estuarine Study)
    - Archaeological Groups, 1990-1991 and undated; 5308; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Archaeological Groups)
    - Atlantic Coast Conservation Association, 1992; 5309; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Atlantic Coast Conservation Association)
    - Audubon Council of North Carolina, 1992-1993; 5310; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Audubon Council of North Carolina)
    - Capital Area Visitors Center, 1976-2001; 5311; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Capital Area Visitors Center)
    - Carolina Charter Tercentenary Commission, 1962-1963; 5312; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Carolina Charter Tercentenary Commission)
      - Brochures, 1963; 23109; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Brochures)
      - Proposals, 1962; 23110; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Proposals)
      - Reports, 1963; 23111; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Reports)
    - Citizens Library Movement, 1937-1999; 5313; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Citizens Library Movement)
    - Coastal Resources Commission, 1989-1999; 5314; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Coastal Resources Commission)
    - Commissions and Committees (general), 1923-1989; 5315; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Commissions and Committees (general))
    - Committees to Preserve Segregation, 1957-1959; 5316; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Committees to Preserve Segregation)
    - Cultural Groups, 1974-1997; 5317; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Cultural Groups)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution, 1994-2001; 5318; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Daughters of the American Revolution)
    - Democratic Party, 1958-1994; 5319; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Democratic Party)
    - Department of Administration, 1979-1992; 5320; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Department of Administration)
    - Department of Agriculture, circa 1910s-1990s; 5321; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Department of Agriculture)
    - Department of Community Colleges, 1980s-1990s; 5322; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Department of Community Colleges)
    - Department of Conservation and Development, 1936-1960s; 5323; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Department of Conservation and Development)
    - Department of Cultural Resources, 1900-2010; 5324; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Department of Cultural Resources)
    - Department of Environment, Health, and Natural Resources, 1958-2006; 5325; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Department of Environment, Health, and Natural Resources)
    - Department of Human Resources, 1997-2004; 5326; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Department of Human Resources)
    - Department of Natural and Economic Resources, 1951-2004; 5327; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Department of Natural and Economic Resources)
    - Department of Public Instruction, undated; 5328; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Department of Public Instruction)
    - Department of Transportation, 1960-2003; 5329; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Department of Transportation)
    - Division of Aging, 1991 and undated; 5330; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Division of Aging)
    - Division of Archives and History, 1949-2006; 5331; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Division of Archives and History)
    - Division of Coastal Management, 1988-1999; 5332; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Division of Coastal Management)
    - Division of Commerce and Industry, undated; 5333; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Division of Commerce and Industry)
    - Division of Emergency Management, 1990-2000; 5334; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Division of Emergency Management)
    - Division of Forest Resources, 1979-1988; 5335; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Division of Forest Resources)
    - Division of Marine Fisheries, 1981-2000; 5336; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Division of Marine Fisheries)
    - Division of Mineral Resources, 1969; 5337; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Division of Mineral Resources)
    - Division of Seafood Marketing, undated; 5338; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Division of Seafood Marketing)
    - Division of Soil and Water Conservation, undated; 5339; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Division of Soil and Water Conservation)
    - Division of State Parks, 1927-2007; 5340; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Division of State Parks)
    - East Carolina Fish, Oyster, Game, and Industrial Association, 1890; 5341; Outer Banks History Center (Folder East Carolina Fish, Oyster, Game, and Industrial Association)
    - Educational Groups, 1901-1937; 5342; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Educational Groups)
    - Environmental Groups, 1990-2001; 5343; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Environmental Groups)
    - First Flight Centennial Commission, 1999-2003; 5344; Outer Banks History Center (Folder First Flight Centennial Commission)
    - First Flight Centennial Foundation, 1998; 5345; Outer Banks History Center (Folder First Flight Centennial Foundation)
    - Fraternal Organizations, 1901-1948; 5346; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Fraternal Organizations)
    - Friends of the Archives, 1992-1996 and undated; 5347; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Friends of the Archives)
    - Garden Club of North Carolina, 1937-1939, 2007; 5348; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Garden Club of North Carolina)
    - Governors Coordinating Committee on Aging, 1956-1963; 5349; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Governors Coordinating Committee on Aging)
    - Historic Albemarle Tour, 1983-1992 and undated; 5350; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Historic Albemarle Tour)
    - Historic Preservation Foundation, 1991-2013; 5351; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Historic Preservation Foundation)
    - Historic Sites: Alamance Battleground-House in the Horseshoe, 1960-1993; 5352; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Historic Sites: Alamance Battleground-House in the Horseshoe)
    - Historic Sites: North Carolina Transportation Museum-Wolfe Memorial, 1959-2006; 5353; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Historic Sites: North Carolina Transportation Museum-Wolfe Memorial)
    - Historic Sites Section, 1975-2004; 5354; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Historic Sites Section)
    - Historical Groups, 1927-2014 and undated; 5355; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Historical Groups)
    - Historical Publications Section, 1958-1996; 5356; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Historical Publications Section)
    - Hospitality and Travel Groups, 1968-1993 and undated; 5357; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Hospitality and Travel Groups)
    - Land Stewardship Council of North Carolina, 1993-1994; 5358; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Land Stewardship Council of North Carolina)
    - League of Women Voters of North Carolina, 1954-1992; 5359; Outer Banks History Center (Folder League of Women Voters of North Carolina)
    - Legal Groups, 1884-1992; 5360; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Legal Groups)
    - Leisure Groups, 1930 and undated; 5361; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Leisure Groups)
    - Medical Groups, 1850-1994; 5362; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Medical Groups)
    - Museum of Art Foundation, 1992; 5363; Outer Banks History Center (Folder Museum of Art Foundation)
    - North Carolina Academy of Science, 1941-1942; 5364; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Academy of Science)
    - North Carolina Airspace Coalition, 1989; 5365; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Airspace Coalition)
    - North Carolina Alliance for Conservation Action, 1991 and undated; 5366; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Alliance for Conservation Action)
    - North Carolina Aquariums, 1984-1999 and undated; 5367; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Aquariums)
    - North Carolina Arts Council, 1996-2006; 5368; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Arts Council)
    - North Carolina Association of Realtors [2 folders], 1959-1973; 5369; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Association of Realtors [2 folders])
    - North Carolina Bar Association, 1915 and undated; 5370; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Bar Association)
    - North Carolina Coastal Federation [2 folders], 1983-2015; 5371; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Coastal Federation [2 folders])
    - North Carolina Conference for Social Services, 1927-1940 and undated; 5372; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Conference for Social Services)
    - North Carolina Environmental Defense Fund, 1990-1991; 5373; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Environmental Defense Fund)
    - North Carolina Fisheries Association, 1993-2001; 5374; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Fisheries Association)
    - North Carolina Folklore Society, 2002 and undated; 5375; Outer Banks History Center (Folder North Carolina Folklore Society)